Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/soniachawla-5a780b38 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Employee Engagement
Job Evaluation
HRIS

Certifications

Accessibility in Action
LinkedIn Certified Professional Recruiter

Sonia Chawla

University Recruiter at Microsoft Gurgaon

Summary

CAREER SUMMARY:

HR Professional with more than 6 years of experience in areas of Campus Recruitments/ relations, Human Resource Management broadly - Talent Acquisition & Management, Compensation & Benefits, Employee Engagement & Development, HR Policies, Performance Management, Reward & Recognition, Career Planning, HR Budgets & Management, Organization Development, HRMS & Training & Development and Management of Change.

In various assignments have worked closely with CEO/ MD/ Director HR/ Head HR/ Business and Functional Heads understanding different aspects of business and the dynamics.

PROFESSIONAL ACHIEVEMENTS:

While in Heidelberg I received "Star Employee of the Month Award" in September, 2011. I was selected in the Top 20 of the High Potentials Scheme since inception (August, 2012). Ranked 3rd in the overall assessment of the Hi-Potentials for the year 2013. Conducted Trainings on Performance Management System, Time Management and Change Management for the Sales & Marketing Team. Led the Change Management towards target orientation for the entire Sales & Marketing team.

Experience

Microsoft University Recruiter November 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months) Gurgaon, India

Part of Microsoft's Global University Relations team. Inspiring students to realize their dreams at Microsoft.

Dell Technologies
Talent Acquisition Sr Analyst
October 2017 - November 2018 (1 year 2 months)
Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Part of Dell's Global University Relations Team and responsible for University hiring & relations for all of Dell's businesses in India.

Dell

Talent Acquisition Analyst July 2016 - October 2017 (1 year 4 months) Bengaluru Area, India

Part of Dell's Global University Relations Team and responsible for University hiring & relations for all of Dell's businesses in India.

HeidelbergCement India Limited
Manager - Human Resources
August 2011 - September 2014 (3 years 2 months)
Gurgaon

Part of the Corporate HR team and responsible for hiring & engagement activities for all of HeidelbergCement's Sales team in India.

Education

Panjab University
BALLB (Hons.), Law · (2006 - 2011)

Welham Girls School (1998 - 2006)